复习练习 6-6：Roy the Rancher。下面开始段落。
Review exercise 6-6. Roy the rancher. Roy's car will arrive around 3 in the
afternoon.
Gary will rest before they ride around the ranch together in the ford. Gary's a grape
grower in northern California and Roy's a rancher in southern California. They were
friends in Paris at the Sorbonne for four years. Roy and Gary had an orange grove
and an apple orchard in Barstow, but the oranges were horrible and the apple trees
were worse. They roamed around Europe for several years until Gary's marriage. He
married Sarah in Bakersfield and had four children, Rachel, Rudy, Randy, and Harry.
Harry was a fairly rude boy and he created rather a lot of trouble between Gary and
Sarah. Gary ordered Harry to shape up or forget working in the yard for extra
money. Harry said he was sorry and the group became friends again. After a long
separation, Gary heard from his friend Roy. Roy was driving through Fresno and
wanted to get together with Gary's family. Everyone gathered around the fireplace to
wait for Gary's old friend. Gary, Sarah, Rachel, Rudy, Randy, and Harry are sitting
in a row near the garage. Roy's car will arrive around 3 in the afternoon.